[ WATER DRIPPING ]
[ CHANGING RADIO STATIONS ]
MAN ON RADIO : They come in here , they 're taking American jobs
from American , hard-working American ...
MAN : Those fucking idiots on this thing .
WOMAN ON RADIO : But I see that another man ...
MAN : Think I have something here .
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
There you go . Know this ?
Gordy ?
You look tired , man .
You look beat .
Your turn to feed Emma ?
No , well , she still has that , um ...
ear infection .
MAN : She 's still got that ? She had that at the christening .
She 's still got it ? Wow .
How 's Wendy holding up ?
Tired . Same as me .
You need anything , Gordon , you let me know , okay ? I 'm here .
Hang in there , man . You 're gonna be fine , all right ?
MAN 2 : Uh-huh . No .
About 15 minutes . Yeah .
Okay , all right , I 'll tell him right now .
[ HANGS UP CAR PHONE ]
That was , uh , Bill Griggs on the phone .
He says he 's getting off the ramp . He 'll be here in a minute .
- Okay . Thank you . - Thank you very much .
You know what ? Can I ask you a quick question ?
Yeah , sure .
- When was the hospital actually closed ? - ' 85 .
- MAN : ' 85 . - GUARD : Yeah .
Yeah , because you know I 'm curious ,
because you know they got you and you got the ... the firearm on .
And it 's not like people are trying to get out , right ?
No , no , not out , in !
You know , kids , delinquents , homeless .
Oh , yeah , a lot of patients ended up in the streets when this place closed down .
And some of them , they come back .
I found a half a dozen squatting up there last spring .
The patients come back ?
Yeah , they come back . I mean , God knows why .
Wait till you see the place .
I mean , Jesus , I 'd rather sleep in the street , personally .
- But , then , you know , I 'm not nuts . - Obviously .
[ CAR HORN HONKING ]
- Hey , there he is . - All right .
- Good luck , fellas . - Thanks .
- MAN : We first in line ? - GORDON : Nope .
Environmental Solutions , American Yankees were up here last week .
Wow . What was their bid ?
Under the Yankees , bid was fast and low .
But that 's the way Griggs likes them . He likes jobs fast , Gordon .
- I like them safe , though . - But we cannot gamble with this .
Gordon , you want me to talk to him ?
Phil , I know what I 'm doing , okay ?
Okay ?
Holy shit ! Look at this .
Look at this .
MAN : 1871 , that 's when she went up , gentlemen .
We called her the " Kirkbride Building " , named after Dr. Thomas Kirkbride .
Well , it 's a pretty simple layout really , you know ?
If you consider a giant flying bat .
You know , the main staff building in the middle , the bat body .
And slanting off to each side are these , like , giant crooked bat wings .
You know , one for female patients , the other for male , you know ?
[ MAKING BAT NOISES ]
A bat .
[ LAUGHS ]
Yeah , believe it or not , this place is listed in the national historic register .
You know , that 's why I can 't tear it down . I 'd love to , you know ?
Only one-tenth of it is salvageable . But the land , the land is priceless .
You know , put up a Wal-Mart maybe , but the town manager wants to reclaim it , so ...
Whoa ! What the fuck is this ?
GRIGGS : Oh , what , are you a little scared , Phil ?
[ GRIGGS LAUGHS ]
This is hydrotherapy . Used to be cutting edge .
They 'd soak the nut jobs in cold water .
I guess that was a way to chill ' em out , I don 't know .
Or they 'd give ' em a lobotomy .
Yeah , yeah , the pre-frontal lobotomy was perfected here at Danvers .
PHIL : Sounds like you 've done your homework .
GRIGGS : Well , you know , my wife Elizabeth , she 's the town historian .
She likes to keep me in the know .
Hey , there 's a fantastic morgue in the basement where they do the post-mortem ...
Bill , Bill , could you show us the problem areas ?
- Yeah . Sure , sure . - Thank you .
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
- PHIL : Feed a fucking army in here ! - [ BRIGGS LAUGHS ]
Well , they did . It was a self-contained town .
Church , movie theater , bowling alley , you know ?
Oh , there 's a lovely cemetery up behind the machine shop .
No headstones , just numbers .
You really ought to check it out . Watch your step here .
This will become the municipal archives , my wife 's department .
GRIGGS : It was a dining area .
GORDON : Is there gonna be a lot of foot traffic ?
GRIGGS : Well , yeah , it 's like a library .
All these tiles will have to go . These are deadly .
- They 're loaded with asbestos , Bill . - GRIGGS : Really ?
You know , the other bids didn 't point that out .
GORDON : Oh , they should have , man . It 's standard .
GRIGGS : All right , I 'm gonna take you to the female wing now . Ward C.
It 'll become Administration , Town Manager 's office .
- Department of Public Works . - PHIL : In other words , your office .
GRIGGS : You better believe it !
Okay , each wing is made of four wards .
Wards A , B , C , and D.
Ward A , which I call the wing tip ,
is the farthest away from the staff building .
This is where they 'd keep the extreme patients .
What do you mean , extreme ?
Well , psychotic .
Keep the most dangerous ones furthest away , right ?
Hey , you 're so smart , Phil . Whoever said you weren 't smart ?
You know what they called Ward A ? The snake pit .
Now , you follow these two down , they 'll take you to C.
But I wouldn 't advise walking on the floors .
- There 's water damage . - How do we get over there ?
GRIGGS : Any of you guys scared of the dark ? What ?
Over here .
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
[ STATIC NOISE ]
GHOSTLY VOICE : Hello , Gordon .
PHIL : Gordy ? It 's me , man . Come on .
Survival rations .
GRIGGS : Yeah , duck and cover , my friend .
Bend over and kiss your ass good-bye .
You know , this place was used as a fallout shelter .
To me , that is a weird idea .
GORDON : All these ducts are gonna have to be wet-stripped . You see this ?
GRIGGS : Yeah .
GORDON : That breaks off , dust gets into the east tunnels .
You 're gonna pollinate the entire building .
GRIGGS : Oh , Jesus , I wouldn 't want that .
GORDON : Believe me , you don 't want that to happen .
PHIL : No , you don 't .
Gordon , let me lead . Hold on .
PHIL : Jesus . Okay .
Yeah , this used to be a solarium . I call it the carpet-toned room .
[ GRIGGS LAUGHS ]
GRIGGS : Well , here we are , gentlemen , Danvers Town Hall .
Reclaiming the dark past to build a brighter future .
Something like that . Huh ?
- Crocidolite . - Crocli ... what ?
- Oh , Crocidolite . - Crocidolite ?
Yeah , worst kind . This is decaying , friable .
Uh , I 'd say circa 1940s .
- Really ? - Yeah .
So , what 's the deal , then ?
Well , if I were you , Bill , I would ... I 'd seal off the whole area .
Full poly , a couple of neg air machines , decon showers , the whole bit .
GRIGGS : You know , OSHA won 't let me start until you guys clean her up ,
and I got to get construction crews in here by Columbus Day . So ...
You got a guesstimate on how long ? Roughly ? Ballpark ? What ?
These rooms , game room , tunnels , I would say ...
Three weeks , minimum .
GRIGGS : Three weeks .
Two . Two weeks .
- Two weeks . - GORDON : Two weeks .
PHIL : Yeah .
You guys Mack and Myer for Hire ? What is it ? Three or two ?
Two . Two weeks .
- Two weeks . - He 's the captain , right ?
You better believe it .
GRIGGS : Well , I guess you guys have seen enough , huh ? Need anything else ?
- GORDON : No . - GRIGGS : All right .
- What 's all this , Bill ? - Ah , they 're punks .
Little motherfuckers come in , and they get high , boot scag , shoot guns .
- Destructive little bastards . - Shoot guns ... at what ? At what ?
Well , hopefully , each other .
- Hey Bill . - GRIGGS : What ?
What is this ?
GRIGGS : Hey , Phil , what , are you checking in ?
Don 't go in there without your bathing suit .
Oh , yeah , this is ... this is seclusion .
That 's what they called the patients rooms back then , seclusions .
It 's some part of some therapy that was big in the ' 70s .
All these cut-outs and ... stuff .
You know , art therapy , creative expression .
You know , it helped them with their ... you know , like , self-esteem .
Yeah .
Helped them feel good about themselves and more at home . It was creepy , huh ?
PHIL : Shades of your childhood , huh ?
GRIGGS : Yeah , there 's a picture of me at summer camp somewhere up here .
PHIL : Huh . Wow .
What do you think was wrong with this one ?
GRIGGS : I don 't know .
Watch out for the broken glass here .
Yeah .
Hey , you know , I got a little time . You want to check out that cemetery ?
- 750 bodies buried there . It 's like ... - Gentlemen , I 'm ... I 'm sorry .
- What , Phil ? - I left a bag . I got to go back .
- Oh , you know where you 're going ? - Yeah , middle of the bat wing , right ?
You got it .
- Okay , I 'll see you down here . - PHIL : I 'll be out !
- Gum ? - No , thanks , man .
You know , I don 't think I ever congratulated you and Wendy on your new addition .
Ah , thanks man . Thanks !
You know , I know how long you both ...
Well , you know , we 're just so happy for you and Elizabeth .
- You wanna see her ? - Oh , yeah . Bring a picture ?
- I 'll show you my baby . - Aww .
Aww .
- Yeah ? - Isn 't she just a doll .
- Emma . - Oh , yeah !
Listen , I 'll match Yankee 's bid .
Well , this isn 't how we normally do the bidding process .
I mean , the deadline 's Friday , paperwork on my desk ...
I know , I know . We 'll be in on Monday , and we 'll be out the following Monday .
- I thought you said two weeks . - One week . I 'll do it in one week .
I 've got four really good guys .
I 'll hire another guy . One week , we 're gone .
- One week ? - One week .
- That 's fast . - Uh-huh .
I 'm good for it . You know I 'm good for it .
I need the job .
I really need this job .
[ BABY CRYING ]
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ BABY CONTINUES CRYING ]
[ SIGHS ]
WOMAN : Roses ? They 're lovely !
What 's the occasion , Gordon ?
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GENERATOR RUNNING ]
[ ELECTRICAL HUM ]
Genny is up and running , sir .
- Take the mask off , Hank . - Are the ACO levels safe , sir ?
Take it off , dickhead .
GORDON : Here 's what I want you to do , okay ?
I want you to go down to the tunnel , hang up those glove bags .
Tag those ducts we looked at this morning .
Use the green slime .
You mean red , right ? Those ducts are hazards , Gordo .
- What ? - Red , right ?
Yeah , red .
Hey ya , Phil . Amy says hi .
Keep it up , dickhead .
Don 't shoot the messenger , Phil . I 'm just relaying information .
She says to me this morning , while we 're laying in bed , to say hi to you .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Keep it up .
Yeah , I got it . That 's the problem , right ?
So dude , how long have you been working with my Uncle Gordon ?
- MAN : Five whole years . - All right .
Was he a slave driver or what ?
Well , Gordon 's a very reasonable man . I 'm the slave driver .
Got a couple of rules though . Safety first , get the job done , second .
And , uh , no drugs on the job , dude .
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
- Woo-hoo ! - What the hell is that ?
So , Mike , you gonna show me the ropes ?
- This the new guy ? - They call it Jeff .
MIKE : It 's Gordon 's nephew .
- Mikey didn 't tell you about these ? - What ?
- You can 't use these . - Why not ?
Rule one , music creates sonic vibrations .
Vibrations jiggle spooge dust into the air .
Gets into the air , it gets into your lungs .
This the kind of music you plan on listening to here , buddy ?
- Yeah . - Yeah , yeah . You trying to kill us all ?
Put it away or play something else , man .
Like Yanni or John Tesh or something , all right ?
HANK : I 'll see you guys at lunch . I 'm going down deep .
MIKE : Later .
[ TURNS DOWN RADIO VOLUME ]
Who 's Yanni ?
HANK : You know , Gordo , you finally landed us the perfect gig .
Next time someone says what we do is crazy ,
you just say , " Yeah , well , we work in an insane asylum . "
You might actually want to be grateful , my man .
You 're about to make some decent money .
Yeah , what ? Five bucks an hour ?
- You didn 't tell him ? - You tell him .
Okay . $ 10,000 bonus . Gordon arranged it with the town .
What 's the catch ?
We got to finish by the 13th .
The 13th ? As in what , this Monday ?
Come on , Gordo , you know this is at least a two-week job .
That 's exactly right . So , we 're gonna work our asses off .
So , what is it ? Ten G 's each ?
If you don 't like it Henry , I 'll give you a ride to the airport right now .
Let it go , Phil .
What about Amy ? You gonna take Amy to the airport ?
She likes to travel .
- I know she likes to travel ... - GORDON : Hank !
GUARD : Hey , guys ! I got your keys for the gate .
GORDON : Thanks , man .
GUARD : So , what do you think , huh ?
Fifteen years really does a number on a place .
You know , it 's hard to believe there used to be over 2,400 patients here at one point .
JEFF : Yeah , so why 'd they close this place down ?
Nearly all these places got closed down in the ' 80s .
Ya know , the budget cuts .
The Feds called it Deinstitutionalization .
So , they just dumped the people on the street ?
Some . Some went to , like , homecare-type programs .
So , the loonies are outside in the real world ,
and here we are with the keys to the loony bin , boys .
[ CHUCKLES ]
Well , it wasn 't just the budget cuts , you know .
What was it , then , Mike ?
Patricia Willard scandal , 1984 .
GUARD : Patricia Willard ?
I don 't recall that .
Patricia Willard , she was committed here in the 1970s by her parents .
Manic depression , that sort of thing . Typical adolescent crap .
But in the 1980s , this new kind of therapy took off ,
Repressed Memory Therapy .
See , the shrinks figured
that with these new techniques they designed , they could release ...
hidden memories of traumatic events in your life : rape , incest .
So Patricia , with the help of her doctors ,
recalls that when she was 10 , her father raped her .
But not once , right ? No , he 'd do it three times a week .
And he didn 't just rape her .
He came into her room at night wearing a black robe .
He 'd take her and drive her to a wooded area
where her grandparents and her mother were .
And they 'd all have black robes on .
They 'd take them off , and group orgies would ensue .
And then they bring out the newborn .
She was forced to watch , as her mother would cut this baby 's heart out
with a stone dagger .
She 'd drink the blood , others would eat the flesh .
Her grandfather and father would fuck her repeatedly .
She was forced to have abortions , and they 'd cook the aborted fetuses .
- Enough ! - MIKE : Huh ?
- This happened here ? - Oh , yeah . Everywhere .
Satanic Ritual Abuse Syndrome was big in the ' 80s .
Destroyed a lot of families .
Patricia was ready to sue hers . It was all set to go to trial , and ...
- What ? - She dropped the suit .
Why ?
MIKE : Well , her parents discovered
a physical examination she 'd undergone about a year prior .
Turns out she was a virgin .
[ MIKE LAUGHS ]
None of it happened . So the family countersues . They win .
That , and the budget cuts .
And ... poof .
- JEFF : So , Mike , is that story true ? - MIKE : Yeah .
How do you know all that stuff , man ?
My dad was a lawyer . He was on the case .
Aw , come on , Mike , don 't be so humble .
His dad 's the state attorney general , so you better watch your ass there , buddy .
Hank , leave it alone , will ya .
You were supposed to carry the torch too , right ? Tufts Law School ?
Hank , drop it .
What were you on there again , Mike ? The one-year plan ?
- Need help with that ? - No , I 'm fine , thank you .
- Jesus ! - Tough weekend , boss ?
No , I think I pulled a muscle or something .
Mike and I called you Saturday night to take you out to Molly 's
for a beer over the winning bid .
Aw , cheers , man , sorry and all . I was trying to catch up on some sleep .
- Baby still got that ear thing ? - Oh , yeah .
- So , Gordy , if we don 't make Monday ... - Oh , Griggs likes jobs done fast .
No , I understand that . But if we lose this bonus ?
We won 't lose the bonus .
Listen , man , I know where this is leading ,
but , believe me , Jeff is young , okay , but he 's not as stupid as he looks .
I 'm not talking about Jeff .
We ran into Craig McManus on Saturday night .
I told him about the job , about the bonus .
He would leave Yankee and work for us in a second .
Now , he has more experience than Hank , and he gives a shit .
Phil , your job here is to keep things on track and to eliminate obstacles .
And that 's what I 'm trying to do , is to eliminate an obstacle .
Jesus , man . We 're talking about Hank here .
Now , listen , if I thought he was a liability , I 'd let you sack him .
As it happens , he 's not .
- And I don 't agree . - I don 't care !
Now , let 's finish the decon chamber . Jesus , Phil .
Fine .
[ ELECTRICAL HUMMING ]
- All right . All right . - Let 's go , turn right , turn right .
Now , when you get it straight , you gotta bring the nose down .
Bring ... Don 't look at me . Look ...
What are you , a lobotomy case ?
- Fuck you , man ! I got it ! - MIKE : Put the nose down !
Turn around ! Jesus !
- MIKE : Nice job , Jeff ! - That wasn 't me , man .
- Yeah . - JEFF : Fuck you , dude .
- MIKE : Just , just wait there . - What ?
MIKE : Just ... hang on .
What the hell ?
Huh ?
Okay , go down and check the breaker box .
No , I can 't do that .
Why ?
I got nyctophobia .
- What ? - Fear of the dark .
Okay . I 'll go check the breaker box .
You ... just try not to break anything , okay , mullet head ?
Thanks , man .
[ ELECTRICAL HUMMING ]
Oww !
[ CHINA BREAKING AND SCREAMING ]
Oh , damn !
[ GROANS ]
Goddamn !
[ BIRDS SINGING ]
- You okay ? - GORDON : Yeah , it 's fine .
- Good first day , Gordo . - Hm-mm .
Listen , Mike needs another hour . The genny carburetor 's acting up .
Okay , but listen , I don 't want anyone hanging around this place after dark .
Okay . No problem .
Good first day , guys .
It keeps up like this , we 'll all be dead by Monday .
Hey , fuck you , Phil !
[ LAUGHING ]
PHIL : See you in the morning .
[ CAR HORN HONKING ]
[ NOCTURNAL ANIMAL SOUNDS ]
[ TAPE RUNNING ]
[ TAPE REWINDING ]
DOCTOR : I know this is difficult , Mary .
And that 's why we 're here to help , okay ?
MARY : I miss Peter .
I miss him so much !
[ MARY CRYING ]
Mary , I want you to try to remember what happened 22 years ago .
On Christmas night in Lowell .
MARY : That 's where we grew up .
DOCTOR : Yes . Can you tell me what happened that night in Lowell ?
- MARY : Nothing happened ! - Mary , something did happen .
DOCTOR : That 's why we have these sessions ,
to help you remember , so you can get better , okay ?
MARY : No . No , I can 't remember .
DOCTOR : File note . Patient is showing extreme agitation .
She is putting her fingers in her mouth .
Mary ... Mary ?
LITTLE GIRL VOICE : Will you share a doll , Mr. Doctor ?
DOCTOR : Who am I speaking with ?
LITTLE GIRL VOICE : Mary got a china doll from her mommy .
And we can 't find it now .
DOCTOR : No , Princess , I haven 't seen it .
DOCTOR : Maybe Billy knows where your china doll is .
PRINCESS : Silly Billy !
[ PRINCESS LAUGHS ]
DOCTOR : Princess , tell me what happened on Christmas 22 years ago in Lowell .
PRINCESS : We got presents .
Mary got a pretty china doll , and Peter got a big old knife .
[ PRINCESS CHUCKLES ]
DOCTOR : Then what happened ?
PRINCESS : Mary 's mommy and daddy went to sleep .
And then we played upstairs .
Peter turned off the lights and hid . And Mary tried to find him .
[ CHILDREN GIGGLING ]
DOCTOR : Who played upstairs , Princess ?
PRINCESS : Mary and Peter , and me and Billy , silly !
DOCTOR : Has Billy told you what happened next ?
PRINCESS : Billy only tells me nice things , Mr. Doctor .
Like , that I 'm pretty .
DOCTOR : Princess , was Simon there that night ?
PRINCESS : Simon ?
Ooh , I don 't know any Simon .
DOCTOR : Billy 's never told you about Simon ?
PRINCESS : No .
I 'm tired , Mr. Doctor .
DOCTOR : Maybe Billy would like to talk now .
PRINCESS : Billy 's asleep , Mr. Doctor .
He 's asleep .
[ GORDON GROANS ]
[ GENERATOR RUNNING ]
[ GORDON BREATHING HEAVY ]
GHOSTLY VOICE : You can hear me .
[ LOUD BANGING ]
Genny 's gassed up and running , sir .
MIKE : Very good . Make sure she stays that way .
I don 't want her dying on us .
MIKE : Put your mask on , Princess .
JEFF : Fuck off . I 'm not your princess , dude .
What ?
JEFF : So , what 's up with Phil and Hank ?
What 's up with Phil and Hank ?
Hank stole Phil 's girlfriend . It 's a nightmare .
You don 't want to get involved .
You especially don 't want to get on Phil 's bad side .
He 'll give you the grunt work , all right ?
[ HANK HUMMING ]
[ REGGAE MUSIC AUDIBLE FROM HEADPHONES ]
[ DROPS SPRAYER ON THE GROUND ]
1884 .
1883 . Fuck , yeah !
[ SCRATCHING WALL WITH A TOOL ]
SINGER ON RADIO : Free at last ! Free at last !
[ RADIO CLICKS ]
PHIL : Yo , Henry , come back .
Hank ? Come back !
Uh , yeah , yeah , Hank here .
PHIL : I want you with Jeff and Mike after lunch , so bring your gear up .
Yeah , all right . Hank out .
[ STUFFING COINS IN THE WALL ]
[ WATER SLOWLY DRIPPING ]
Gordo !
Got your wallet .
Nice grab . Okay , ladies , time to thank Uncle Gordy for lunch .
JEFF : Thanks , Uncle Gordon !
PHIL : Your turn tomorrow , Hank . Where 's Mike ?
The equipment room , looking for those lost cartridges .
Jesus , Phil !
I told you , I didn 't want anyone wandering around here by themselves !
Okay , boss . It won 't happen again , okay ?
Do you got my scratch tickets ?
Yeah , I got ' em right here , Bubba . I 'm comin ' .
Let 's see , Hank , your scratch tickets .
There you go . There 's one .
HANK : Oh , Phil , these are Jubilee . You know I play Blackjack .
- Yeah , here 's one for you , too . - Hey , Phil ... fuck you !
GORDON : Mike , come in .
MARY : I can 't talk anymore . I am too tired .
DOCTOR : It appears Miss Hobbes is now entering a dissociative state ,
rubbing her eyes , appears to be switching to an alternate personality .
Uh , yeah , I 'll be there in a minute .
- DOCTOR : Mary ? - BOY 'S VOICE : Hello , sir .
DOCTOR : Well , hello , Billy . How have you been ?
BILLY : Never better , sir .
DOCTOR : Billy , where does the Princess live ?
- BILLY : In the tongue . - DOCTOR : Why the tongue ?
BILLY : Because she 's always talking , sir .
DOCTOR : And where do you live , Billy ?
BILLY : I live in the eyes . You know that .
DOCTOR : Remind me , though . Why the eyes ?
BILLY : Because I see everything , sir .
DOCTOR : And where does Simon live , Billy ?
Where does Simon live ?
Hey , what 's mortified pride ?
Says here , three patients were committed in 1889 because of mortified pride .
Let me see that .
1889 . Where 'd you get this ?
JEFF : Under some boxes , man . It 's fucking intense , some of the shit ...
When Phil calls lunch , it means lunch . Understood ?
Sorry , no cartridges . I gotta go pick some up at Grossman 's .
Listen to this .
17 were committed due to disappointed expectations .
Henry , they 're talking about you .
They would 've committed your ass back then .
Hey , what do you have to do now to get committed ?
Mortify someone 's pride ?
Simple .
You kill someone .
Nah , that won 't get you committed . But it 'll get you in jail .
If you get caught .
John Hinkley , temporary insanity .
He 's not in jail . He 's in a nut house . Right , Mike ?
That defense never works .
Most people are cognizant of their actions when they murder .
Homicide implies a motive .
Oh ... God , Mike .
How did you fail law school ? You 're good .
Yeah , what are you , dude ? A lobotomy case ?
[ CHUCKLING ]
PHIL : Jeff , come on , man .
[ TALKING LIKE A BABY ]
[ JEFF GIGGLING ]
- Hey ! Hey ! - Mike !
- Mike ! - PHIL : Mike .
C 'mon , I 'm just fucking around , Gordo .
- PHIL : Don 't hurt him ! - MIKE : It 's all right .
The Ice Pick method .
Insert a thin metal pipette into the orbital frontal cortex
and enter the soft tissue of the frontal lobe .
A few simple smooth , up and down jerks to sever the lateral hypothalamus .
All resulting in a rapid reduction of stress for our little patient here .
Total time elapsed , two minutes . Only side effect ?
Black eye . Recommended treatment ...
Sunglasses .
[ CLAPPING ]
Brilliant ! Very good .
All right . Let 's go back to work . Come on .
I wasn 't kidding back there , man . You 're smarter than this crap job .
You should be using your head , buddy .
Yeah , um , I gotta get a part from Gordon 's van .
Make sure mullet head here knows how to operate that thing .
Hey , Mike , come on , don 't forget this .
- You know how to ride a lawn mower ? - Yeah .
Oh , then , you 're golden . Basically the same thing .
So , I don 't know .
Just push it in to that mid section there and just start over there , all right ?
I 'm gonna take a smoke break .
We just had a break .
[ SOUL ECSTASY BY THE INNER THUMB PLAYING ]
Hey , Jeff !
- What 's up ? - You know what a whale is ?
Yeah , I know what a whale is .
[ TURNS DOWN MUSIC ]
A whale is a big time gambler .
I got this buddy , right , he deals out at Foxwoods .
12 hours , and this whale has the house down 300 grand , right ?
As this guy 's leaving , takes his car keys ,
and drops them in my friend 's pocket .
- HANK : You know what they 're for ? - What ?
Porsche 911 .
It 's true , man , and that was the tip .
Fucking tip !
What 's your point ?
Just have an exit plan , dude .
If you stick with this job too long , it will mess you up , man .
It gets inside of you ... the stress .
You see ?
Already an itty bitty piece of this shit may have gotten into your lungs , man .
It incubates in your lungs ,
and tissue begins to grow around it like a ... like a pearl .
Like a time bomb .
Time you hit 30 ... Boom !
You 're drowning in your own lung fluid .
Look at you , you 're not even wearing your mask now .
- Hey , where 's your mask ? - Me ? Nah ...
Nah , buddy , I 've learned to sublimate my fear .
'Cause I got a fuckin ' exit plan , man .
I have a way of dealing with the stress .
You think Mikey reads all those books for fun ?
Nah , man , he 's got an exit plan , let me tell you .
If stress gets too intense on this job , he 'll bolt .
He 's gonna go back , finish law school , pass the bar ,
get the big , juicy cases , make his dad proud .
That 's his exit plan .
Phil , Jesus ... Phil 's got his stress reducer .
He 's got his plan . I 'm sure he 'll tell you about it someday .
Then there 's Uncle Gordo .
Hey , did you know if he didn 't get this gig , he 'd have to fold H.E.C. ?
Yep . Man , he can 't even have an exit plan .
Fiber has always been his life .
It was over there . It is here . Imagine that stress .
Hey , let me tell you something , buddy , you better hope ,
hope , you got some of Gordo 's genes , though . ' Cause Gordo ...
Jesus , Gordo is the Zen master of calm .
I 've never seen old Gordo lose it .
I don 't know , though , man .
The last few months , Gordo , I 'm seein ' some cracks .
Ya know , I worry .
Mikey knows what I 'm talking about , right , Mikey ?
He does have the new baby , ya know .
It should be the joy of his life , dude .
Hank , when you and Amy have a kid , you 'll see how hard it is .
Me and Amy ? A kid with Amy ? Nah , I just fuck her to beat on Phil .
MIKE : Hey , get off your ass . I want my bonus .
[ TURNS OFF RESPIRATOR ]
[ SIGHS ]
Hi , Wendy ?
I know , but we need to talk .
Because we have to .
[ GENERATOR RUNNING ]
Would you let me finish ? Would you ... ? Hello ?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
Baby needs a new pair of shoes .
Let 's do this thing .
[ JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING DISTANTLY ]
HANK : Silver .
Yeah , baby , gold , gold .
[ HANK LAUGHING ]
Fucking eyeballs . Jesus Christ !
They ought to be worth something . All right .
[ LOUD THUMP ]
[ JAZZ PLAYING FROM HEADPHONES ]
[ HIGH-PITCHED NOISE ]
[ GROANS ]
HANK : Yeah , baby , check that out .
What the fuck is that ?
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ MUSIC PLAYS FROM HEADPHONES ]
[ GASPS ]
[ MOVEMENT BEHIND HANK ]
[ HANK GASPING ]
[ LOUD CLANGING ]
[ HANK GASPING AGAIN ]
[ RATTLING FENCE ]
[ HANKS HITS A FENCE ]
God !
Fucking birds !
[ HANK CONTINUES TO GASP ]
Jesus .
Oh , damn .
[ HANK YELPS ]
[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
[ INSECTS BUZZING ]
JEFF : So what 's the verdict ?
GORDON : I 'm getting nothing here . He 's not even left his answering machine on .
JEFF : You a ...
- JEFF : You try Amy 's yet ? - GORDON : Do you know her number ?
Okay , I 'll try information .
No , fuck , give me the phone .
Huh ?
I know the number , Gordon . Give me the phone !
PHIL : Thank you .
Hi ! Hi , it 's me . Yeah , uh ...
Wait ... Wait a second . What ?
What are you talking about ?
When ? When ? Slow down . When did this happen ?
Really ?
No , no , no . No , no , no . No , no .
You hang in there . I 'll call you back .
Well , our favorite piece of shit , Hank ,
went to Amy 's last night , packed his car ,
told her that he found his meal ticket ,
and then bolted to Miami to Casino School .
That lucky fuck ! And he probably scored on a scratch or something .
I warned her , didn 't I ? I fucking warned this bitch , didn 't I ?
She said that he left without saying anything ?
Gordon , it 's Hank . He 's totally unreliable .
Mike , call McManus . Call Craig . See if he 's still available .
PHIL : Gordy ?
Gordy , this is a blessing .
We replace this asshole , and we move forward .
What 's the problem ?
Something 's not right here . Some ...
- What 's the matter ? - [ SIGHS ]
Who are those two guys you were talking to yesterday ?
- What guys ? - I saw ya .
- Now , what were you talking about ? - What is this ?
I 'm asking you a question . What were you talking about ?
Okay .
- Are you questioning my performance ? - I don 't know . Should I be ?
- Mike , call McManus . - Don 't walk away from me !
Don 't ever walk away from me !
You gonna hit me ?
[ GORDON WALKING UP STAIRS ]
PHIL : You think I 'm doing a bad job , Mike ?
MIKE : No , you 're doing fine .
This used to be a great deal .
Steady gigs , joking around , beers after work .
Hey , look ! It says here , eight were committed for uncontrolled passion .
Then Emma came .
PHIL : Don 't look at me like that , man .
You know it 's why we lost the last two gigs .
He 's tired , and he overbid .
- Gordon loves being a father . - Yeah , now he does , now he loves it .
But it was never in his heart . This was Wendy 's idea .
Look , Phil ...
Just ' cause you say you don 't want something ,
it doesn 't mean you don 't want it .
Now , six years ago I didn 't want to be a lawyer , but now I 'm thinkin ' I might ...
Wait ! Wait ! Who the fuck are you kidding ?
You shuck fiber with us , in there , okay ?
Look ... That 's not what I 'm talking about .
I 'm talking about ... fatherhood is screwing this guy 's head up ,
and it 's fucking his job up .
At the very least , Mike , he should 've canned Hank 's ass six months ago , and you know it .
What are you looking at ? Where you going , Mike ?
- MIKE : I 'm gonna go take a piss . - You got 25 !
[ BIRDS AND INSECTS CHIRPING ]
Hello , Wendy ?
Can we talk ?
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
Wendy ?
I wanna ask you something .
Can you forgive me ?
JEFF : Uncle Gordon !
Wendy ?
Hello ?
Gordon ?
- JEFF : Sorry . - Hey , man .
JEFF : I didn 't see you on the phone .
- Sit down . Sit down . - JEFF : Thanks .
I just ... I just came to ...
Thank you for giving me this job , you know ?
JEFF : I mean , I want to let you know I 'll bust my ass for you , okay ?
I know that . I know that .
So , don 't stress out , all right ? Things will work out .
JEFF : I 'm here for you , and I 'm gonna bust my ass , all right ?
Yeah .
- Family , man . - Yeah .
- So , was that Aunt Wendy ? - Yeah .
- How 's she doing ? - She 's good .
She 's , uh ... tired , you know ?
It 's when ...
- Kids tire you out sometimes . - JEFF : Yeah , no , I know .
My dad 's got the photos back from the christening .
Yeah ?
- Emma looks pretty pissed off . - Yeah , she 's pretty pissed .
[ MARY CRYING ]
DOCTOR : Why are you crying , Mary ?
MARY : I miss my family .
How come they don 't visit , Doctor ?
DOCTOR : Mary , can you tell me how you got those scars on your chest ?
MARY : How many times do I have to tell you ?
MARY : I fell off my bike when I was a girl .
DOCTOR : Is that what you remember , Mary ?
MARY : Yes !
DOCTOR : Now , can you tell me who the Princess is ?
- MARY : No idea . - DOCTOR : And who Billy is ?
MARY : I don 't know anyone named Billy .
- DOCTOR : Who is Simon , Mary ? - MARY : I have no idea who Simon is !
- MARY : I am sick of this ! - DOCTOR : Mary , calm down .
- MARY : I just want to go back to my room ! - DOCTOR : Mary ?
[ MARY GASPING ]
DOCTOR : Mary ?
BILLY : Mary is asleep , sir .
DOCTOR : Billy , why won 't you tell me what happened in Lowell .
I know you saw what happened .
BILLY : You know perfectly well what happened , sir .
DOCTOR : But Mary needs to know what happened , Billy .
- She needs to remember . - BILLY : No !
DOCTOR : Well , then , maybe Simon would like to tell me what happened .
- BILLY : He 's asleep . - DOCTOR : Help me wake Simon .
- BILLY : No ! - DOCTOR : We must wake up Simon .
- BILLY : I won 't ... scared ! - DOCTOR : Billy , we have to wake up Simon .
You should take a shower , Gordon .
You shouldn 't go home with that shit on you , man .
What 's the stupidest thing you 've ever done ?
You mean , besides coming to work for you ?
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
Uh ... I would have to say ...
I would have to say introducing Hank to Amy .
That was pretty fucking stupid . I wish I had that one back .
I wish I had that one back .
I hit Wendy .
What ?
It was Friday night . I wanted to celebrate getting this job .
I had the flowers . I had the champagne .
I went into the kitchen . She was cooking pasta .
I wanted to kiss her .
She turned around , and before I knew it ,
there 's a pot of boiling water all over my leg .
I don 't know if it was the dog barking , I don 't know if it was Emma crying ,
but I slapped her .
I hit my wife .
I love my wife .
It was an accident .
But I slapped her for it .
I 've tried to talk to her on the phone , but she wouldn 't listen .
Where are you staying ?
A motel .
You don 't tell the other guys about this .
Oh , come on , man .
You were right about Craig . You should give him a call .
You know , uh , they , uh , those kids , the other day ...
I had a conversation with those fuckin ' graffiti artists ,
and they will not be coming back our way again .
I spoke to ' em , I said , " If I see you again , I 'm calling Security , " so ...
Anyway , so , that 's taken care of , all right ?
Okay .
Hang in there .
Take a shower .
Get that shit off of you .
[ NOCTURNAL NATURE SOUNDS ]
GHOSTLY VOICE : Hello , Gordon .
Do you know who I am ?
WENDY : Roses ? They 're lovely !
What 's the occasion , Gordon ?
[ WENDY LAUGHING ]
WENDY : Not here , Gordon . Later .
Watch out !
[ GORDON AND WENDY SCREAMING ]
GHOSTLY VOICE : Do it , Gordon !
[ WENDY SCREAMING ]
[ CRICKETS CHIRPING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GORDON CONTINUES GROANING ]
[ OWL HOOTING ]
[ GORDON YELLING ]
[ HEAVY BREATHING ]
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
Hey .
- You 're up early . - Yeah .
Guess I wasn 't the only one who couldn 't sleep .
I got , uh , I got Craig coming in tomorrow . Okay ?
You okay ?
I want to go home .
I 'm gonna go inside .
Okay ?
I gotta go .
[ GEESE HONKING ]
It 's gonna get ugly .
[ FLOOR SCRAPER RUNNING ]
Ah , Jesus Christ !
- Jeff , what did you do ? - JEFF : It wasn 't me , man !
I 'm gonna go check the breakers .
Mike !
- What ? - Take a break with me .
- I can 't . I gotta go check the breakers . - PHIL : Let the kid do it .
MIKE : Well , the kid can 't . He 's got nyctophobia .
Mike .
Okay , all right .
Fuck .
- We got a problem . - What ?
We have a problem , and I want you to know that this is not easy for me .
Look at me . This is not easy for me , do you understand ?
All right .
- We need to talk about Gordon . - What about him ?
He needs to take some time off , Mike .
- Why ? - Because he 's becoming a liability .
I .. Phil , look , I can see why you 're a little paranoid .
Can ya ? Do you know that he hit his wife ?
PHIL : He hit Wendy , Mike .
Now , I 've got Craig coming over tomorrow .
If Griggs hears about this , you understand what that means , right ?
You want to lose this gig ? You want to lose the bonus ?
'Cause that 's what 's gonna happen .
So , what do we do ?
Okay , you listen to me . You follow my lead .
You let me handle this , okay ? I don 't give a shit what happens .
Fuck ! I 'm in charge now .
So , what did he say ?
It think it might happen Saturday . I don 't ...
Hey .
MIKE : We were just talking about your nephew .
And how he 's coming along . That sort of thing .
And how 's he coming along ?
[ ELECTRICAL HUMMING ]
[ JEFF CLIMBING STAIRS ]
Hank ?
Yo , dude , hello !
Hank !
You 're in some deep shit , you know that ?
What are you doing here ?
What am I doing here ? What are you doing here ?
Everyone thinks you 're in Miami at that Casino School .
Fucking Gordon and Phil want your head , man !
So , dude , did you score on a scratch , or what ?
What are you doing here ?
Listen , I forgot something . I 'll be back .
You know , um , he just needs a little motivation .
- That 's ... pretty much it . - Yeah .
What do you think , Phil ?
Same , I think he 's a little slow . But , uh ...
With Hank gone and Craig coming on , we 'll pick up the slack .
MIKE : I mean , I 'll motivate him ... the little mullet head .
He may be party in the back , but I 'll make sure he 's business in the front .
- What time is it ? - I think it 's noon . About noon .
- Lunch time . - MIKE : Yeah .
Want to place the order ?
Yeah . Yeah , sure , sure .
MIKE : I think it 's Phil 's turn , though , right , Phil ?
- Fuck it , Mike . Let 's flip for it . - What ?
- Let 's flip for it . - Where 'd you get that ?
PHIL : Found it . It might even be worth something , too . You ready ?
- MIKE : You found it ? - PHIL : Yep .
Call it in the air . Heads or tails ?
MIKE : Heads .
Tails . Get going , loser .
What ?
- What ? - Hey , Uncle !
Gordon ?
- JEFF : I found Hank ! - Gordon ?
What do you want , Jeff ?
I found Hank .
PHIL : What the fuck are you talking about ?
I just found Hank ... in the stairwell . He was just standing there .
Don 't be a fucking idiot , okay ?
I 'm not a fucking idiot ! I swear to God , I saw him !
If he 's in Miami , Jeff , why would he be here ?
How could that be possible , Jeff ?
I don 't know , but I saw him !
PHIL : You know what ? Go back to work , we 'll bring you lunch .
Where was he , Jeff ?
In the staircase , next to the equipment room .
Wait ... wait a minute . You believe him ? You believe this punk , Gordon ?
Gordon ! Oh , for Christ 's sakes , Mike !
This is so goddamn ridiculous ! Gordon !
- If he 's in Miami , why would he be here ? - Ask him yourself , Phillie . Right up there .
We 're gonna do that , Jeff . We 're gonna do that , my man .
That 's what we 're doing , man . That 's where I 'm taking you .
We 're gonna do that .
- JEFF : I 'm telling you , he 's up there . - PHIL : Where is he ?
He was standing right there .
It 's fucking weird , but he 's right here . I 'm telling you . He 's right ...
Right over where , Jeff ?
I swear he was . I 'm not lying . Why would I make this up ?
PHIL : Nice going ... Jeff .
Okay , listen to me guys , now . You heard me on the phone with Amy .
Am I right ? She said Hank went to where ? Miami ! Okay ?
Now , we heard it , we all heard it , right ?
No ... no , we didn 't .
What ?
- I want to go to lunch . - No , you stay where you are .
What are you saying , Gordon ?
You told us that 's what she said , but we didn 't hear her say it .
We saw you on the phone , we heard you on the phone , we didn 't hear Amy .
Right , so what you 're saying to me is that it wasn 't Amy on the phone ?
Is that what ... Mike , now , come on , man . This is what I 'm talking to you about .
- Mike . Mike , give me that cell phone . - Why ?
'Cause I want to talk to Amy .
What ? I spoke to Amy . You don 't need to speak to Amy .
- Give me the cell phone . - Don 't give him the fuckin ' cell phone .
- Give me the cell phone . - Mike , that 's what I 'm trying to tell you .
- Give me the cell phone . - He 's losing it , man .
Mike , give me the cell phone !
This is what I 'm telling you . He 's losing it , man !
- Look at him ! He 's losing it , man ! - Give me the fuckin ' cell phone !
[ WALKING UPSTAIRS ]
- What the fuck was that ? - It 's Hank !
JEFF : It 's Hank !
Okay , okay . Jeff , Mike , go downstairs . Make sure he doesn 't come around .
- You , you come with me . - Hey ! Fuck you !
You come with me . Let 's go .
- Mike ! - PHIL : Come on , Jeff .
- Oh , wait , you heard him go that way . - Take the tunnels . They 're safer .
Safer ?
Gordo , this could be anybody . Could be squatters , could be kids .
Come on , Phil , slow down , man . He 's not fucking down here .
God !
Hey , Gordo , did you hear that ?
I thought I heard something down there , in the tunnels . Did ya hear it ?
No . No , it 's this way .
Gordo , I 'm going down in the tunnels , all right ? You follow up top .
Mike ! Mike , we stick to ...
Fuck this .
What the fuck , Phil ? Man , slow down .
- So fucking stupid ! Why ? - Shh ! Shh !
[ ELECTRICAL HUMMING ]
- I don 't hear anything . - PHIL : Shh ! Shh !
Give me your torch .
This is fucking dumb . He 's not gonna be down there .
Shut up ! I want you to stay right there .
You see or hear anything , you call me . You understand me ?
- I left my walkie in the van ! - Stay there !
- Phil , wait ! - PHIL : What , Jeff ?
When I saw Hank , I think he had blood on his hand .
Stay there .
DOCTOR : And , Billy , you understand that you , the Princess and Simon
are all in Mary ?
BILLY : Yes , sir .
DOCTOR : And if Mary is sick , then , you are sick , too . All of you .
DOCTOR : You want Mary to get better , right , Billy ?
- BILLY : Yes ! - DOCTOR : So , help her , Billy .
Tell me about that night in Lowell , Billy .
BILLY : We were playing hide n ' seek , sir .
[ KIDS LAUGHING ]
BILLY : Mary was looking at her new doll , and she was looking for Peter .
It was real dark .
Phil ?
BILLY : No , I won 't tell !
Mary 's a good girl ! She doesn 't need to know !
- DOCTOR : What ? - BILLY : What Simon did !
DOCTOR : To who , Billy ? To who ?
[ BILLY CRYING ]
BILLY : To Peter !
- DOCTOR : What did Simon do to Peter , Billy ? - BILLY : I won 't do it !
DOCTOR : Tell me , so that we can make Mary ...
[ FAST FORWARDING TAPE ]
JEFF : Fuck !
[ JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING IN THE DISTANCE ]
GHOSTLY VOICE : Gordon .
[ ELECTRICAL HUMMING ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
MAN : What are you doing here ?
DOCTOR : Billy , I need to talk to Simon .
BILLY : He made me do it . It was awful .
- DOCTOR : Billy , wait . - BILLY : It was awful . No !
[ GHOSTLY VOICE LAUGHING ]
MAN : What are you doing here ?
[ GENERATOR WINDING DOWN ]
- DOCTOR : We need to wake up Simon . - BILLY : No , it 's too awful !
DOCTOR : Wake up Simon .
MAN : What are you doing here ?
What are you doing here ?
[ RADIO CLICKS ]
GORDON : Phil . Phil , I think I found Hank .
[ GASPING ]
HANK : What are you doing here ?
[ RADIO CLICKS ]
PHIL : Gordon , come back .
Gordon , come back .
- Yeah . - PHIL : Where are you ?
- Ward A. Third floor . - PHIL : I 'm coming .
[ GENERATOR KICKS BACK ON ]
GHOSTLY VOICE : Hello , doc .
DOCTOR : Simon ?
SIMON : You know who I am ?
DOCTOR : Billy has told me a lot about you .
SIMON : Billy is a smart boy .
DOCTOR : What happened on Christmas night in Lowell ?
SIMON : Use your imagination .
DOCTOR : I 'd rather you tell me , Simon .
SIMON : Peter was naughty , doc .
DOCTOR : What did Peter do ?
SIMON : He shouldn 't have done it , doc .
DOCTOR : Tell me , Simon .
SIMON : He scared Mary , doc .
[ MARY SCREAMING ]
SIMON : He crept up behind her in the dark .
And he scared her .
[ MARY SCREAMING ]
SIMON : Mary fell down , doc .
[ CHINA BREAKING AND MARY SCREAMING ]
SIMON : She fell on her doll .
It cut her up , doc . It cut her up real bad .
She needed someone to help her .
So I introduced myself .
Hello , Mary .
And I told her to cut up Peter , doc .
Do it , Mary .
[ SIMON LAUGHING ]
SIMON : To cut him up real bad .
[ PETER CRYING ]
SIMON : Good thing his knife was brand-new .
[ SIMON LAUGHING ]
SIMON : Real sharp .
[ SIMON CONTINUES LAUGHING ]
SIMON : And then , just so her mommy and daddy wouldn 't get mad ...
[ SIMON CHUCKLES ]
SIMON : ... I told her to cut them up , too .
- Do it . - [ MARY 'S PARENTS SCREAMING ]
SIMON : There was a lot of blood , doc .
So much blood .
But Mary wanted to do it .
Do it , Mary !
So she did it .
[ JEFF SCREAMING ]
Gordon , come back , please .
[ INSECTS BUZZING ]
GORDON : Who is that ?
Gordon , it 's Jeff . I 'm by the van .
[ RADIO CLICKS OFF ]
I 'm sorry , man . I was freaking out . The lights went out .
I got these in the van . Is that okay ?
[ BIRDS SINGING ]
PHIL : Come back .
Come back .
This is Gordon .
PHIL : We found the one ...
The one responsible .
[ DROPS RADIO ]
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
You 've got to be kidding me . Freaking beautiful .
Gordon !
Hello ? Hello ? Hello ?
Phil ?
McManus is here . Where are you guys ?
I mean ... I mean ...
He was a liability .
Who did this ?
[ SIGHS ]
Well ...
I mean ... He brought it on himself .
Didn 't he ? I mean , it 's typical ... Typical Henry .
Wrong place at the wrong time .
You did this .
PHIL : Gordon .
I need you to wake up ...
and take ... a really ...
really ...
good look at him .
Oh , Jesus .
What are you doing here ?
GORDON : It 's okay , Hank . Hank , it 's okay , it 's me .
You hang in there , brother . You hang in there .
We 'll try and get you some help , okay ?
You know what I wouldn 't do ? I wouldn 't tell anybody about this .
Because if they find out about Hank , they 're gonna find out about the others .
You did this .
What are you ... ? What are you doing here ? Huh ?
You got those guys , didn 't ya ? You hired those guys to do this ?
Gordy , you are asleep .
- You hired those guys to kill him . - You 're asleep .
- Where are the others ? - Open your eyes .
- Where are they ? - You 've got to wake up .
- You tell me where they are . - Would you wake up ?
- Tell me . - Would you wake up ?
I am fucking awake !
CRAIG : Hey ! Gordon !
Who you talking to , man ?
Gordon ?
CRAIG : I 'm a little confused here , man .
What 's , uh ... Hey , what is it ?
Hey , Gordon !
[ CRAIG YELLS ]
[ HANK GROANING ]
No !
SIMON : Do it , Gordon !
What are you doing here ?
[ CARNIVAL-LIKE MUSIC PLAYS ]
DOCTOR : Why did you do it , Simon ?
SIMON : Because Mary let me , doc .
They always do .
[ CARNIVAL-LIKE MUSIC CONTINUES ]
What are you doing here ?
[ HANK SCREAMING ]
SIMON : They always do .
[ SIMON LAUGHING ]
PHIL : You know what I wouldn 't do ?
I wouldn 't mention this to anyone , Gordy .
- Gordy . - PHIL : I wouldn 't tell anybody about this .
Because if they find out about Hank , they 're gonna find out about the others .
I found Hank , Gordy .
He 's hurt , and he said you did it to him . Is that true ?
Gordy ? Gordy !
[ PHIL YELLING ]
[ SIMON LAUGHING ]
GORDON : Who did this ?
PHIL : Well ...
He brought it on himself .
Didn 't he ?
Wrong place at the wrong time .
[ MIKE SCREAMING ]
[ SIMON LAUGHING ]
- GORDON : Where are the others ? - PHIL : Gordy , you are asleep .
Uncle Gordon !
PHIL : Wake up !
The lights went out .
I 'm sorry , man . I was freaking out .
I got these in your van . Is that okay ?
[ JEFF YELLS ]
[ INSECTS BUZZING ]
PHIL : Gordy .
I need you to open your eyes now .
Wake up .
And remember .
WENDY : Roses ? They 're lovely !
What 's the occasion , Gordon ?
[ WENDY LAUGHS ]
WENDY : Not here , Gordon . Later .
Watch out ! Gordon !
[ GORDON AND WENDY SCREAMING ]
WENDY : Oh , my God , Gordon ...
No !
Stop !
No , stop , Gordon ! No !
SIMON : Do it , Gordon .
[ WENDY SCREAMING ]
[ DOG BARKING ]
[ BABY CRYING ]
[ DOG YELPING ]
[ BABY 'S CRYING CONTINUES ]
SIMON : Do it , Gordon .
[ STRAINED CRYING ]
SIMON : Do it now .
GORDON : No !
[ WATER DRIPPING ]
[ GORDON SNIFFLING ]
GORDON : Wendy . Wendy , it 's me . Please don 't hang up . Please .
I just want to say how sorry I am for what 's happened .
I am so sorry .
I am so lonely here .
[ CRYING ]
I want to come home .
I want to hold you . I want to hold my baby .
Can you forgive me ?
DOCTOR : And where do you live , Simon ?
SIMON : I live in the weak and the wounded ...
doc .
[ CHOKE CHAIN BY LOU BARLOW PLAYS ]